TUTUL HOSEN

Dhaka, Bangladesh

tutulhosen2022@gmail.com

01551678133

linkedin.com/in/tutul-hosen-9659b3228

Summary

Hi,

My name is Tutul Hosen, from Bangladesh.

I am a Software engineer at MysSoft Heaven BD LTD.

I am working with PHP language. My maximum project has been developed with most powerful framework like Laravel and some of Codelgniter.

Also I have been working with WordPress Theme Development.

Thank You

Experience



Software Engineer

Mysoftheaven (BD) LTD.

Dec 2022 - Present (1 year)

Hi,

I have been working with Laravel, Codelgniter, WordPress



PHP Web Developer

CodersTrust Bangladesh

Jun 2021 - Feb 2023 (1 year 9 months)

Education



Jagannath University, Dhaka

Bachelor of Science - BS, Geography

Jun 2014 - Dec 2019

Skills

API Development • CodeIgniter • jQuery • AJAX • PHP • Laravel • MySQL • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • JavaScript • HTML5